http://www.royalhydraulics.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Toggle Navigation
HomeDistributionAccumulators Inc.BenshawBrennanBondioli & PavesiContinental HydraulicsContinental ValvesCurtiss-Wright (Penny & Giles)DMICDynex-RivettEaton-HydrolineEaton-InternormenEmmegiFlowEzyHawe HydraulikHilco-HilliardManuliMagnaloyAccessoriesMechanical Drive CouplingsReservoirsMarzocchiMillerMoogMP FiltriOrtmanNoshokOilgearRycoStauffYukenYoung PowertechLinecardProductsAccumulatorsCylindersHydrolineMillerOrtmanElectronicsFiltrationEaton InternormenFlowezyHilco-HilliardMP FiltriStauff FiltrationFittingsFlow-metersGear PumpsBondioli & PavesiYoung PowertechHeat ExchangersHose & AdaptersManuliRycoJoystick ControllersLinear SensorsManifoldsMechanical Drive CouplingsMotors - Electric & PistonMotors - ServoMotor StartersPower Units & SystemsPressure GaugesPumpsMedium PressureHigh PressureVery High PressurePiston PumpsVane PumpsRKP PumpsGear PumpsOilgear PumpsPVWJ PumpsPVG PumpsPVV PumpsPVWC PumpsReservoirsRotary SensorsServo ActuatorsServo Proportional ValvesServo ValvesSolenoidsSuppressorsTransducers & TransmittersValvesBall ValvesYuken ValvesDMIC ValvesAbout UsRoyal Systems GroupContact UsNewsNewsletterCOVID-19
Privacy Policy
Print
Email
Details
Created: 24 February 2011
Last Updated: 29 June 2016
Hits: 24271
The policies below are applicable to Royalhydraulics.com, produced and maintained by Royal Hydraulics, Inc. ("RHI").
We at Royal Hydraulics, Inc. believe very strongly in personal privacy. For that reason, it is our policy not to sell or share any of our visitors' personal information. Additionally, it is our policy to employ certain security measures protecting, to the extent we are able, the integrity of the data transmitting personal and financial information from our visitors to us.
RHI collects personally identifying information only during electronic catalog registration. This information is specifically and knowingly provided by users for the express purpose of purchasing merchandise from RHI. RH may use such information for its internal purposes, including but not limited to special promotions, incentives, and targeted shopping.
RHI reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users, either through a notice posted on Royalhydraulics.com or by email, of the existence of a new privacy policy or any updates.
ATTENTION CHILDREN: IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 18, YOU MUST GET PERMISSION FROM YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN BEFORE YOU DO ANY OF THE FOLLOWING ON OR THROUGH THE CATALOG :
SEND ANY INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF OR OTHERS
BUY ANYTHING
IF YOU GET PERMISSION FROM YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN TO SUBMIT YOUR NAME TO THE CATALOG, YOU SHOULD NEVER USE YOUR FULL NAME. JUST SUBMIT YOUR FIRST NAME OR INITIALS.
Terms & ConditionsLegal NoticesPrivacy PolicySite Map
